(Auto Search) Just type what are you looking for? 

### Select a Language

City of Reading  
Government

City of Reading, Pennsylvania  
Website Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the ReadingPA.gov on the World Wide Web. Our web site is designed to make it easier and more efficient for Reading, PA citizens and businesses to interact with their City Government. But as with all online resources, we appreciate that many visitors to our sites will be concerned about their privacy. The City of Reading is committed to preserving you privacy when you visit our sites.  
  
This policy addresses the collection, security and access to information that may be obtained through the use of the sites maintained by the City Of Reading. This policy covers the following topics:  
  
• Information We Collect  
• Public Disclosure  
• Access  
• Choice  
• Cookies  
• Security  
• Linking  
• Information Disclaimer  
  
Information Collected  
If you visit a web site maintained by the City of Reading to read or download information, we collect the following information:  
  
• The name of domain; for example, “xcompany.com” if you use a private internet access account, or “yourschool.edu”, if you are connecting from a university domain;  
• An IP address; a number automatically assigned to your computer when you are using the internet;  
• The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;  
• The Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site;  
• The pages you visit within the City’s site; and  
• The links made to other web sites through this site.  
  
This information is collected for statistical analysis using standard third-party software programs to create summary statistics. The statistics are used for the purpose of determining what information is of most and least interest to all visitors and identifying system performance or problem areas. This information is not collected for commercial marketing purposes and the City does not sell information collected online for commercial marketing purposes.  
  
If, during your visit to the City’s web site, you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information, we will collect such information. Examples of personally identifiable information may include:  
  
• An email address if you are communicating to us through email;  
• Information you voluntarily submit to the City for the purposes of completing or submitting an application or form online; and  
• Other information volunteered, such as survey information or content of email.  
  
In general, please note the information collected, whether or not personally identifiable, is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video and other graphic formats you send us. Information is retained in accordance with existing laws and other City policies.  
  
**Public Disclosure**  
As a general rule, the City does not disclose any personally identifiable information collected online except where you have given us permission, or where the information is public information under the Pennsylvania Right to Know Act 65 P.S. 66.1 et seq., or other applicable laws. Visitors should be aware that information collected by the City on its website may be subject to examination and inspection, if such information is a public record and not otherwise protected from disclosure.  
  
**Access**  
Any personally identifiable information you enter in a user profile will be open and accessible to you for review and modification. If you have any questions or comments about the information presented in this Privacy Policy, you can contact the [This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.](mailto:webmaster@readingpa.org)  
**Choice**  
You may decline participation in any activity that asks for information (i.e., surveys or emails). Your choice to not participate will have no effect on your ability to access information on the City’s web sites.  
  
**Cookies**  
To better serve you, we occasionally use “cookies” to customize your browsing experience. Cookies are simple text files stored by your web browser and they provide a method of distinguishing among visitors to the web sites.  
  
Cookies created on your computer by using our web sites do not contain personally identifiable information and do not compromise your privacy or security. We use the cookie feature to store a randomly generated identifying tag on your computer.  
You can refuse the cookie or delete the cookie file from your computer at any time by using any one of a number of widely available methods.  
  
**Security**  
The City has taken steps to safeguard the submission of information by implementing detailed technology and security policies. Security measures have been integrated into the design, implementation and day-to-day operations of the entire operating environment as part of our continuing commitment to the security of electronic content as well as the electronic transmission of information.  
  
**Link Disclaimer**  
**Information Disclaimer**  
Information provided on the City’s web sites is intended to allow the public immediate access to public information. While all attempts are made to provide accurate, current and reliable information we recognize the possibility of human and/or mechanical error. Therefore, the City of Reading, PA, its employees, officers and agencies expressly deny any warranty of the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of any information published by this system and shall not be held liable for any losses caused by reliance upon the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of such information. Any person who relies upon such information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk.  

City Business Information

SearchSearch ...    

 **QUICK LINKS I**  

 **QUICK LINKS II**  

+82

°

F

H: +89°

L: +68°

Reading

Tuesday, 10 August

See 7-Day Forecast

|     |     |     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Wed | Thu | Fri | Sat | Sun | Mon |
|     |     |     |     |     |     |
| +94° | +94° | +92° | +84° | +83° | +77° |
| +69° | +68° | +68° | +67° | +58° | +66° |

Copyright © 2024 [City of Reading, PA. All Rights Reserved.](https://www.readingpa.gov/ "City of Reading, PA. All Rights Reserved.")

815 Washington St, Reading PA 19601

[1-877-PAREADING  
(1-877-727-3234)](tel:+18777273234)
